[
    {
      "question": "Which platform does the Hogwarts Express leave from?",
      "choices": ["Nine and three-quarters", "Ten and a half", "Nine and four-quartes"],
      "answer": "1",
      "difficulty": "easy"
    },
    {
      "question": "Who stopped Harry and Ron from going through platform nine and three-quarters?",
      "choices": ["Duddly", "Dobby", "Malfoy"],
      "answer": "2",
      "difficulty": "easy"
    },
    {
      "question": "In which movie do dementors board the Hogwarts Express?",
      "choices": ["First movie", "Second movie", "Third movie"],
      "answer": "3",
      "difficulty": "easy"
    },
    {
      "question": "Where did Harry and Ron crash the flying car?",
      "choices": ["The lake", "Whomping Willow", "Forbidden forrest"],
      "answer": "2",
      "difficulty": "easy"
    },
    {
      "question": "Who in the movies turned out to be a werewolf?",
      "choices": ["Remus Lupin", "Sirius Black", "Severus Snape"],
      "answer": "1",
      "difficulty": "easy"
    },
    {
      "question": "What are the words that wipe the Marauder's Map blank?",
      "choices": ["I solemnly swear I am up to no good", "Mischief managed", "I stuck Mrs. Norris in a suit of armor"],
      "answer": "1",
      "difficulty": "medium"
    },
    {
      "question": "Who does everyone think harry resembles the most?",
      "choices": ["Voldemort", "Hagrid", "His mom"],
      "answer": "3",
      "difficulty": "medium"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is Gringotts?",
      "choices": ["Bank", "Candy store", "Village outside Hogwarts"],
      "answer": "1",
      "difficulty": "medium"
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is Harry bringing to the Yule Ball?",
      "choices": ["Luna Lovegood", "Cho Chang", "Parvati Patil"],
      "answer": "3",
      "difficulty": "medium"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the name of Weaslys house?",
      "choices": ["Weasly-castle", "The dragon's nest", "The Burrow"],
      "answer": "3",
      "difficulty": "medium"
    },
     {
      "question": "What is the name of the wizard newspaper?",
      "choices": ["The Daily Prophet", "Wizard news", "The Daily newspaper"],
      "answer": "1",
      "difficulty": "hard"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which Hogwarts house was Cedric Diggory part of?",
      "choices": ["Gryffindor", "HufflePuff", "Slytherin"],
      "answer": "2",
      "difficulty": "hard"
    },
    {
      "question": "What job do Hermioneâ€™s parents have?",
      "choices": ["Works at the Ministry of Magic", "Professors at Hogwarts", "Dentists"],
      "answer": "3",
      "difficulty": "hard"
    },
    {
      "question": "What potion do you drink if you want good luck?",
      "choices": ["Aging Potion", "Felix Felicis", "Polyjuice Potion"],
      "answer": "2",
      "difficulty": "hard"
    },
    {
      "question": "What was in Hermione's hand when she was petrified?",
      "choices": ["A photo", "A piece of paper", "A flower"],
      "answer": "2",
      "difficulty": "hard"
    }
 ]